<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Openinitiatives on Public Money, Public Code</title>
    <link>/openinitiative/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Openinitiatives on Public Money, Public Code</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/openinitiative/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>All Public Signatures</title>
      <link>/openinitiative/all-signatures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/openinitiative/all-signatures/</guid>
      <description>This is the complete list of all the people who signed the open initiative and agreed to have their names made public. 0 people have expressed their support already – are you one of them?
The list is updated hourly.
  Name Country Comment      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Almost done...</title>
      <link>/openinitiative/confirm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/openinitiative/confirm/</guid>
      <description>Check your email inbox now You are almost finished! You will receive an email with a link for the final confirmation of your signature soon. Please check your spam folder if you do not receive the mail within the next 15 minutes.
Thank you for signing the open initiative for Public Money, Public Code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dziękujemy za podpisanie!</title>
      <link>/openinitiative/success.pl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/openinitiative/success.pl/</guid>
      <description>Twój podpis został potwierdzony Dziękujemy Ci za podpisanie otwartej inicjatywy &amp;ldquo;Public Money, Public Code&amp;rdquo;. Twoje wsparcie wiele dla nas znaczy.
Jeśli zgodziłeś/aś się aby Twoje imię zostało dodane do publicznej listy, Twoje imię pojawi się na liście wszystkich podpisów w przeciągu następnej godziny. Jeśli zgodziłeś/aś się by otrzymać więcej informacji, będziemy stale informować Cię o nowościach związanych z tą kampanią przez pocztę email.
Następne kroki Prosimy, pomóż nam nadając swojemu podpisowi większy impakt i podziel się tą kampanią z przyjaciółmi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grazie per aver firmato!</title>
      <link>/openinitiative/success.ms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/openinitiative/success.ms/</guid>
      <description>La tua firma è stata confermata Grazie per aver firmato la lettera aperta &amp;ldquo;Public Money, Public Code&amp;rdquo;. Il tuo supporto significa molto per noi.
Se hai autorizzato l&amp;rsquo;aggiunta del tuo nome all&amp;rsquo;elenco pubblico dei firmatari, apparirà nell&amp;rsquo;elenco di firme entro la prossima ora. Se ha autorizzato la richiesta di ricevere ulteriori informazioni, ti manterremo informato sulle notizie concernenti questa campagna via email.
Prossimi passi Per favore aiutaci dando alla tua firma un grande impatto condividendo questa campagna con i tuoi amici.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prawie zrobione...</title>
      <link>/openinitiative/confirm.pl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/openinitiative/confirm.pl/</guid>
      <description>Check your email inbox now Już prawie skończyłeś/aś! Wkrótce otrzymasz wiadomość na swój adres email z linkiem do ostatecznego potwierdzenia Twojego podpisu. Prosimy, sprawdź swój folder spamu jeśli nie otrzymasz wiadomości w ciągu następnych 15 minut.
Dziękujemy Ci za podpisanie otwartej inicjatywy Public Money, Public Code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quasi fatto...</title>
      <link>/openinitiative/confirm.ms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/openinitiative/confirm.ms/</guid>
      <description>Ora controlla la tua casella di posta elettronica Hai quasi finito! Riceverai presto una email con un link per la conferma finale della tua firma. Controlla nella tua cartella dello spam se non ricevi l&amp;rsquo;email nei prossimi 15 minuti.
Grazie per aver firmato la lettera aperta per Public Money, Public Code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you for signing!</title>
      <link>/openinitiative/success/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/openinitiative/success/</guid>
      <description>Your signature is confirmed Thank you for signing the open initiative &amp;ldquo;Public Money, Public Code&amp;rdquo;. Your support means a lot to us.
If you opted-in to having your name added to the public list, your name will appear on the list of signatures within the next hour. If you opted-in to receive further information, we will keep you informed about news concerning this campaign via email.
Next Steps Please help us by giving your signature a huge impact and share this campaign with your friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutti i firmatari pubblici</title>
      <link>/openinitiative/all-signatures.ms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/openinitiative/all-signatures.ms/</guid>
      <description>Questa è la lista completa di tutte le persone che hanno firmato la lettera aperta ed hanno acconsentito a render pubblico il loro nome. 0 persone hanno già espresso il loro supporto, sei uno di loro?
Questa lista è aggiornata ogni ora.
  Name Country Comment      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wszystkie publiczne podpisy</title>
      <link>/openinitiative/all-signatures.pl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/openinitiative/all-signatures.pl/</guid>
      <description>To jest lista wszystkich ludzi którzy podpisali otawrtą inicjatywę i zgodzili się by upublicznić ich imiona. 0 ludzi wyraziło już swoje wsparcie – czy jesteś jednym z nich?
Ta lista jest aktualizowana co godzinę.
  Name Country Comment      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>